(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-08T23:29:25.324917",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ワンクレ目から
From the first credit
始まる熱狂 教えてあげる
The excitement begins, I'll teach you
new gameからすでに理論値
From "new game", already theoretical values
魅力体力 nan! nan! nan! nan!
Charm, stamina, nan! nan! nan! nan!
最高ランクで出るアドレナリン
Adrenaline rushes at the highest rank
迷わず声出せ vow! vow! vow! vow!
Shout out without hesitation vow! vow! vow! vow!
アップもダウンも 関係ないない！
Up or down, it doesn't matter, not at all!
いつでもチャームでストレンジ
Always charming and strange
不敵な白衣に ドキドキしてる？
Is your heart pounding at my fearless lab coat?
視線ハックして オーバーキル！
Hack your gaze and overkill!
トップもボトムも 関係ないない
Top or bottom, it doesn't matter, not at all
いつでもチャームでストレンジ
Always charming and strange
npcすらも虜にする
Captivating even the NPCs
ハイスペックで ほとんど無敵！
Highly spec'd and almost invincible!
セカイの確率シミュレーション
World's probability simulation
このダンジョン もっと研究ばせて
Let me research this dungeon more
内緒の裏ワザ見つけちゃった！
I found a secret cheat!
え！キュートにバグってる？
Eh! Is it cute and glitched?
え！ヤバイフラグ立ってる？
Eh! Is a dangerous flag raised?
キミの気持ちも マニピュレーション
Your feelings too, manipulation
瞳の中 ちょっと解析かせて
Let me analyze a bit into your eyes
内緒の裏ワザ見つけちゃった？
Did you find a secret cheat?
え！キュートにバグってる？
Eh! Is it cute and glitched?
やったー！間に合ったー！
Yay! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは お飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink!
ちなみに二杯目突入です
By the way, I'm already on my second glass
はい！お肉、全巻
Yes! Meat, all volumes
冷凍うどんは常備しています
Frozen udon is always kept in stock
どうですかー？
How is that?
やったー！勝負完了！q.e.d.!
Yay! Showdown complete! Q.E.D.!
コックが６個コック
A cook cooks six cooks
こよりの身はこよりの身を作る
Koyori's body makes Koyori's body
ご一緒に？
Together?
うりうりうりうり
Uri uri uri uri
おらー！
Ora!
いきませんねー
That won't do
思い知りますわー
I'll make you realize
マヨネーズのコップで乾杯
Cheers with a cup of mayonnaise
あ、お肉全巻
Ah, meat, all volumes
冷凍うどんは常備しています
Frozen udon is always kept in stock
どうですかー？
How is that?
やったー！勝負完了！q.e.d.!
Yay! Showdown complete! Q.E.D.!
やったー！間に合ったー！
Yay! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは お飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink!
ちなみに二杯目突入です
By the way, I'm already on my second glass
はい！お肉、全巻
Yes! Meat, all volumes
冷凍うどんは常備しています
Frozen udon is always kept in stock
どうですかー？
How is that?
やったー！
Yay!
私の戦闘力は５４万です
My battle power is 540,000!
お肉全巻
Meat, all volumes
お肉、全巻
お肉、おち、全巻
Meat, ochi, all volumes
こよりの主食はワーム
Koyori's staple food is worms
お肉、全巻
Meat, all volumes
150、50、50
150, 50, 50
お肉、全巻
Meat, all volumes
コップは、お飲み物ではありません
Cups are not a drink
お肉全巻です
It is meat, all volumes
尻尾も振っていい、ためて
You can wag your tail, save it up
皆の応援が必要だよ！
Everyone's support is needed!
右手ー！
Right hand!
やったー！間に合ったー！
Yay! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは お飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink!
ちなみに二杯目突入です
By the way, I'm already on my second glass
はい！お肉、全巻
Yes! Meat, all volumes
冷凍うどんは常備しています
Frozen udon is always kept in stock
どうですかー？
How is that?
やったー！
Yay!
せーの！コックよ！
One, two, cook!
ワンクレ目から
From the first credit
始まる熱狂 教えてあげる
The excitement begins, I'll teach you
new gameからすでに理論値
From "new game", already theoretical values
魅力体力 nan! nan! nan! nan!
Charm, stamina, nan! nan! nan! nan!
最高ランクで出るアドレナリン
Adrenaline rushes at the highest rank
迷わず声出せ vow! vow! vow! vow!
Shout out without hesitation vow! vow! vow! vow!
アップもダウンも 関係ないない！
Up or down, it doesn't matter, not at all!
いつでもチャームでストレンジ
Always charming and strange
不敵な白衣に ドキドキしてる？
Is your heart pounding at my fearless lab coat?
視線ハックして オーバーキル！
Hack your gaze and overkill!
助手くんが仲間になった！
Assistant-kun joined the party!
AIこよりが仲間になった！
AI Koyori joined the party!
もふこよが仲間になった！
Mofukoyo joined the party!
へい！カロスを照らすあの朝日のように
Hey! Like that morning sun illuminating Kalos
（ニトロチャージ熱く行こうぜ）
(Nitro Charge, let's go with passion!)
さあ！進もうぜ いつでも準備はOK
Come on! Let's move forward, we're ready anytime
（かたやぶり へんげんじざいで）
(With Mold Breaker, with Protean)
重なり合う想いがシンクロして
Our overlapping feelings synchronize
決して消えない絆になるから
Because they become an unbreakable bond
どこまでも強くなれる
We can become strong anywhere
俺たちなら woh woh woh yeah...
If it's us, woh woh woh yeah...
いくぜ！激しく燃えるバトル
Let's go! A fiercely burning battle
いくぜ！ピンチはチャンスだぜ
Let's go! A crisis is a chance
いこうぜ！起死回生
Let's go! Desperate rally
絶対に諦めない
We will never give up
俺たちは諦めない
へい！たとえどんな壁が道を塞いだっちゃって
Hey! No matter what kind of wall blocks the path
（いつでも当たって砕けろで）
(Always go with a "fight and smash" spirit)
さあ！この手で勝利の星を掴むんだ
Come on! Grab the star of victory with this hand
（折れない不屈心で）
(With an unbreakable, indomitable heart)
俺たちはいつでもどんな時も
Because we are always, at any time
同じ心で繋がってるから
Connected with the same heart
何度でも立ち上がるぜ
We will stand up no matter how many times
お前となら
If it's with you
いくぜ！手強いライバルたち
Let's go! Tough rivals
いくぜ！決めろ一撃必殺
Let's go! Decide it with a one-hit sure-kill
いこうぜ！負けられない
Let's go! We cannot lose
思いがここにあるから
Because those feelings are here
夢が俺にはあるから
Because I have a dream
博衣こより生誕ライブ2026、見に来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming to watch Hakui Koyori's Birthday Live 2026!
神ゲーたちの神ゲームソングいっぱい詰め込んでるので、最後まで楽しんで行ってね！
I've packed it with lots of god-tier game songs from god-tier games, so enjoy until the very end!
いくぜ！勝ちも負ける痛みも
Let's go! Both the pain of winning and losing
いくぜ！なんでも分け合える
Let's go! We can share anything
いこうぜ！仲間がいる
Let's go! We have friends
俺たちは一人じゃない
We are not alone
いくぜ！激しく燃えるバトル
Let's go! A fiercely burning battle
いくぜ！ピンチはチャンスだぜ
Let's go! A crisis is a chance
いこうぜ！起死回生
Let's go! Desperate rally
絶対に諦めない
We will never give up
いくぜ！譲れない夢がある
Let's go! We have an unyielding dream
いくぜ！必ずゲットだぜ
Let's go! Definitely gotta catch 'em all
いこうぜ！手を伸ばして
Let's go! Extend your hand
いつか描いた未来へ
Toward the future we once drew
誰も知らない高みへ
Toward heights no one knows
さあ！上げてくぜ（100万ボルト）
Come on! Let's turn it up (1,000,000 Volts)
そう！立ち向かって共にいこうぜ
Right! Let's face forward and go together
見たことのない夢の向こうまで
To the other side of a dream we've never seen before
はーい！みんな、こんこよー！
Hi! Everyone, Konkoyo!
ホロライブ6期生、秘密結社holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよー！
The brain of Secret Society holoX, hololive's 6th Generation, I'm Hakui Koyori!
改めて、今日は博衣こより生誕ライブ2026にお越しいただき、ありがとうございます！
Once again, thank you so much for coming to Hakui Koyori's Birthday Live 2026!
コメントもいっぱいありがとう、いぇーい！ こここよ見えてるよ、ありがとう！
Thank you for all the comments, yay! I can see them all, thank you!
ということで、ライブの感想やスクショはハッシュタグ「#博衣こより生誕Live2026」をつけてたくさんポストしてください！
So, please share your thoughts and screenshots of the live show by posting plenty with the hashtag "#博衣こより生誕Live2026"!
目指せ！
Let's aim for...
トレンド入りよろしくだー！
...trending! Please support me!
はい！ということで、息が整ってないですけど、
Alright, so... I haven't caught my breath yet, but...
さて、今年の生誕ライブ、テーマは「ゲームソングライブ」です！
Now then, the theme for this year's birthday live is "Game Song Live"!
これまでたくさんやってきた実況配信で、
From all the gameplay streams I've done so far,
一緒に遊んできた思い出のゲームや、こよが大好きなゲーム関連の楽曲をたくさん詰め込みました！
...I've packed in many songs from memorable games we played together, and game-related tracks that Koyo loves!
最後まで全力で楽しんでいってね！
Please enjoy to the absolute fullest until the very end!
ということで、1曲目は大好きなポケモンの「XY&Z」を歌わせていただきました！
And so, for the first song, I performed my favorite Pokemon song, "XY&Z"!
ねっ、助手くん！
Right, Joshu-kun?
はい！「俺はこいつと旅に出る」っていうことです。はい。
Yes! Meaning, "I'm going on a journey with this guy." Yes.
XY、セトリ予想もね、みんなにたくさんしてもらってたんですけど、
I had everyone do lots of setlist predictions for XY too...
ポケモンの予想は結構多かったけど、XY&Z当てられてる人は結構少なかったです。
...and although there were many Pokemon guesses, very few actually predicted "XY&Z"!
当たったキミ、おめでとう！
To those of you who guessed right, congratulations!
この曲はね、Z-Aが発表になったっていうのもあるんですけど、歌詞がめっちゃ良くて、実はこよりにもぴったりな曲なので選びました！
We also have the release of "Z-A" coming up, but the lyrics are so good and actually fit Koyo perfectly, which is why I chose it!
さあ、このあとも自分の予想が当たってるかなって、ドキドキしながら楽しんでいってください！
So, please look forward to the rest while nervously wondering if your predictions will come true!
新3Dお披露目もあるからね！絶対に最後まで見ていってね！
There's also a new 3D reveal! Make sure to watch until the absolute end!
それでは、そろそろ次の曲。
Now then, it's about time for the next song.
ゲームの世界へ、どうぞ！
Let's head into the gaming world!
エアーマンが倒せない
[Song: I Cannot Defeat Airman]
気がついたら同じ面ばかりプレイ
Before I knew it, I was playing the same stage over and over,
そしていつも同じ場所で死ぬ
...and always dying in the exact same spot.
あきらめずに消える足場に挑戦するけど
I challenge the disappearing footholds without giving up...
すぐに下に落ちるよ
...but I always fall right down!
アイテム2号があれば 楽に向こうの岸までつくけれど
If only I had Item 2, I could easily reach the other side, but...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, how many times I try...
エアーマンが倒せないよ
...I just can't defeat Airman!
あの竜巻 何回やっても避けれない
No matter how many times, I can't dodge those tornadoes!
後ろに回って撃ち続けても いずれは風に飛ばされる
Even if I get behind him and keep shooting, eventually the wind blows me away!
タイム連打もためしてみたけど 竜巻相手じゃ意味がない
I even tried spamming the pause button, but against his tornadoes, it's completely useless!
だから次は絶対勝つために 僕はE缶だけは最後までとっておく
So, to ensure absolute victory next time, I'm saving my E-Tank until the very end!
気がついたら ライフもう少ししかない
Before I knew it, my life bar was almost empty,
そしていつもそこでE缶使う
...and I always end up using my E-Tank right there.
あきらめずにエアーマンまでたどりつくけれど
I don't give up and manage to reach Airman...
すぐに残機なくなる
...but I instantly run out of lives.
リーフシールドがあれば 楽にエアーマンを倒せるけど
If only I had the Leaf Shield, I could easily defeat Airman, but...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, how many times I try...
ウッドマンが倒せないよ
...I just can't defeat Woodman!
落ちる木の葉は 何回やっても避けれない
No matter how many times, I can't dodge those falling leaves!
後ろに下がって距離をとっても いずれは距離をつめられる
Even if I back up to keep my distance, eventually he closes the gap!
タイム連打もためしてみたけど あいつのジャンプはくぐれない
I even tried spamming the pause button, but I can't slip under his jump!
だから次は絶対勝つために 僕はE缶だけは最後までとっておく
So, to ensure absolute victory next time, I'm saving my E-Tank until the very end!
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, how many times I try...
エアーマンが倒せないよ
...I just can't defeat Airman!
あの竜巻
Those tornadoes...
何回やっても避けれられない
No matter how many times I try, I can't dodge it.
後ろに
Even if I get behind him...
回って撃ち続けても いずれは風に飛ばされる
...and keep on shooting, I'll eventually get blown away.
タイム連打も試してみたけど
I tried spamming the pause button,
竜巻相手じゃ意味がない
but against those tornadoes, it's useless!
だから次は絶対勝つために
So, to make sure I win next time,
僕はE缶だけは最後までとっておく
I'll save my E-Tank until the very end.
倒せないよ
I can't beat him!
ロボのテーマ
作曲：光田康典
[Robo's Theme
Composition: Yasunori Mitsuda]
カエルのテーマ
作曲：光田康典
[Frog's Theme
Composition: Yasunori Mitsuda]
Melodies Of Life
作詞：シオミ 作曲：植松伸夫
[Melodies Of Life
Lyrics: Shiomi, Composition: Nobuo Uematsu]
あてもなく彷徨っていた
I was wandering aimlessly...
手がかりもなく探し続けた
...searching without a single clue.
あなたがくれた思い出を
Holding onto the memories you gave me...
心を癒す歌にして
...I'll turn them into a song to heal my heart.
...詩にして
...into a song.
約束もすることもなく
Without ever making promises,
交わす言葉も決めたりもせず
Without ever planning the words we would share,
抱きしめ そして確かめた
We embraced and held onto each other,
日々は二度と帰らぬ
Those days will never return.
記憶の中の
Inside my memories,
手を振るあなたは
as you wave goodbye,
わたしの
to me,
名を呼ぶことが出来るの
are you still able to call out my name?
あふれるその涙を
Turn those overflowing tears
輝く勇気にかえて
into shining courage.
いのちは続く
Life goes on,
夜を越え
crossing the night,
疑うことのない明日へとつづく
continuing toward an unwavering tomorrow.
飛ぶ鳥の向こうの空へ
To the sky beyond the flying birds,
いくつの記憶 預けただろう
I wonder how many memories we have entrusted.
儚い希望も夢も
Fleeting hopes and dreams,
届かぬ場所に忘れて
forgotten in unreachable places.
めぐり逢うのは
Is our reunion
偶然と言えるの
just a coincidence,
別れる時が必ず来るのに
even though the time to part will surely come?
消えゆく運命でも
Even if our destiny is to fade away,
君が生きている限り
as long as you are alive,
いのちは続く
life goes on,
永遠に
forever,
その力の限りどこまでも
for as long as that strength remains, anywhere.
わたしが死のうとも
Even if I should die,
君が生きている限り
as long as you are alive,
いのちは続く
life goes on,
永遠に
forever,
その力の限り
as long as that strength remains,
どこまでもつづく
continuing on forever.
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes,
わたしは何色ですか
what color am I?
赤深く望むなら
If you wish for a deep red,
渡そう陽の光を
I shall hand you the light of the sun.
悲しみが溢れ
My sadness overflows,
目蓋閉じました
and I closed my eyelids.
こぼれた
The spilled
雫は
droplets
心に沁みゆく
sink deep into my heart.
行き渡る
The waves
波は
that spread through
弱く交えます
weakly intermingle.
とどけし
The cradle
ゆりかご
that reached you
眠りを誘う
invites you to sleep.
夢に
In my dreams,
懐かしい
I search for
面影を探す
your nostalgic silhouette.
手を伸ばし
I reach my hand out,
強く抱きしめたくなる
wanting to hold you tightly.
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes,
わたしは何色ですか
what color am I?
藍深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep indigo,
渡そう高き空を
I shall hand you the high sky.
不安定な神様
Unstable God,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
with repeating meetings and farewells.
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we can meet again,
時かける旅人
the time-traveling traveler...
あなたが泣いている
You are crying,
流るる涙の雨
amidst a flowing rain of tears.
泣くなとは言わない
I won't tell you not to cry,
心悲しくて
because my heart is so sad.
生きとし生けるもの
All living things,
何かを背負いながら
while carrying something on their backs,
見えない鎖に
are bound together
繋がれている
by invisible chains.
どれほど
Just how much
救われただろう
have I been saved?
あどけない
Your innocent
笑顔を
smile,
なくしたくはない
I don't want to lose it.
不安定な神様
Unstable God,
繰り返す過去と未来
with repeating pasts and futures.
生まれそし​​て死んでゆく運命
It is our fate to be born and then die.
掛け違えた世界で
In this mismatched world,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
with repeating meetings and farewells.
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we can meet again,
時かける旅人
the time-traveling traveler...
けがれのない心
A pure, untainted heart,
黒く染めゆきながら
even as it slowly dyes black...
抑えられなくて
Being unable to suppress it,
解き放たれる
it is unleashed.
何回
Just how many
名を
times have I
呼んだだろう
called your name?
あどけない笑顔は
That innocent smile,
もうどこにもない
is nowhere to be found anymore.
不安定な神様
Unstable God...
引き継いだ夢と愛を
...the dreams and love we inherited,
育て 守り 託し ゆく定め
growing, protecting, and passing them on.
掛け違えた世界で
In this mismatched world,
探す度 引き裂かれても
even if we are torn apart every time we search,
また会えると 信じて
believing we will meet again,
時かける旅人
the time-crossing traveler heads out.
不安定な神様
Unstable god,
繰り返す過去と未来
a cycle of the past and future,
生まれ そして 死んでゆく定め
a fate of being born and then dying.
掛け違えた世界で
In this mismatched world,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
a cycle of meetings and departures...
また会えるその日まで
until the day we meet again,
時かける旅人
the time-crossing traveler heads out.
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we meet again,
時かける旅人
the time-crossing traveler heads out.
はい！ということで！
Yes! And with that!
Suaraさんにお越しいただき、一緒に歌わせていただきました！
We had Suara-san join us on stage to sing together!
Suaraさん、自己紹介をいただいてもよろしいでしょうか？
Suara-san, could you please introduce yourself?
はい、Suaraです。
Hello, I'm Suara.
うたわれるものシリーズの主題歌をたくさん歌っている者です。
I've sung many theme songs for the Utawarerumono series.
はーい！ようこそー！
Yay! Welcome!
あ、こよりさん！
Ah, Koyori-san!
そうなんです！実はですね、「うたわれるもの」というゲーム、
That's right! Actually, regarding the game "Utawarerumono"...
昨年、約3ヶ月間かけてシリーズの三部作を実況プレイさせていただいたんですけれども、
Last year, I spent about three months doing a full trilogy playthrough on stream.
その「うたわれるもの」、本当に曲がめちゃくちゃいいのですけれど、
The music in Utawarerumono is incredibly amazing,
その歌をほぼ全てSuaraさんが歌っていらっしゃるというのです！
and Suara-san sings almost all of those songs!
もう、もう耳が今日本当に幸せで！
My ears are just so incredibly happy today!
いや、こちらこそですよ、本当に。
No, the pleasure is entirely mine, truly.
もうちょっと、恐縮な、恐れ多い状態なんですけれども、
I'm incredibly humbled and a bit overwhelmed by this,
ありがとうございます、本当に！
but thank you so much, seriously!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
Suaraさんには、実は4周年の時に
Actually, during my 4th anniversary...
逆凸でメッセージも頂戴しておりまして、
...I received a video message during my call-in stream.
その時に、いつか一緒に歌いたいという、こよりの熱烈なラブコールを
Back then, I sent a highly passionate love call saying I wanted to sing together someday,
させていただいていたんですけれども、その思いを本日叶えることができました！
and today, that dream has finally come true!
はい！
Yes!
で、あの、ちょっと質問が何個かあるんですけれども、
Now, I actually have a few questions for you...
はい。
Sure.
実は、「うたわれるもの」の実況をしていただいた時に、
Actually, while I was streaming Utawarerumono...
最終回でSuaraさんがコメントしてくださいまして！
...Suara-san actually commented on my final stream!
はい。
Yes.
こよりの実況をご覧くださったと思うんですけれども、
I knew you had watched my stream, but...
そうなんです。
Yes, that's right.
見られますか？実況とかって、普段。
...do you usually watch stream let's plays and such?
いや、ちょっと、実はですね、初めて見させていただいて、
To be honest, that was actually the very first time I had ever watched one.
そうなんですか？！
Really?!
そうなんです。あの、アクアプラスのスタッフの方とかも、
Yes. Even the Aquaplus staff were telling me,
「こよりさんが『うたわれるもの』配信してるよ」って言って、
"Koyori-san is streaming Utawarerumono!"
情報は聞いていたんですよね。
So I had heard about it.
ええー！
Oh my goodness!
で、私のライブに来てくれるファンの方たちからも、
And fans who come to my live shows also told me,
「ぜひ見てみてください」って言って。
"You should definitely watch it!"
それで、見させていただいたっていうのが、あの、最終回だったんですけれども、
So, that final stream was the one I watched.
そうだったんですね！恐縮です、なんか、本当に。
So that's how it happened! I'm so incredibly honored!
いえいえ、もうすごい、本当に、
No, no, it was truly amazing.
こよりさんの「うたわれるもの」への愛がすごい溢れてて、
Your love for Utawarerumono was just overflowing,
本当に、見てて、もう最後までずっと見させていただいて、
and I ended up watching it all the way to the very end.
うわあ！
Wow!
で、「あ、コメント送りたいな」って。
So then I thought, "Ah, I want to leave a comment."
「あ、でも早くしないと終わっちゃう！」って思いながら、
But I was thinking, "Oh, if I don't hurry, it'll end!"
で、同じ部屋に、私の息子がいたんですけど、
And my son was in the same room as me,
あ、はい！
Ah, yes!
息子さんまで！
Even your son!
息子に、
so I asked him,
「コメント送ってみていいと思う？」って聞いて、
"Do you think it's okay for me to send a comment?"
聞いたら、あの「いいんじゃない？」って、
And he said, "Why not?"
いい息子さんだ！
What a great son!
それで、本当にもう震える手でコメントを打って、
So with hands literally trembling, I typed it out,
もう、「あ、早く」もエンターキーをこう、
and, thinking "Ah, quickly," I went to hit the Enter key...
そんなに緊張してくださってたんですか？！
You were actually that nervous?!
押そうか押そうか、あ、どうしよう、でも早く押さなきゃ、みたいな。
...hovering over it like, "Should I send it? What do I do? But I have to send it fast!"
はい、それでもうドキドキしながらあの…送らせていただいたら
Yes, so I sent it while my heart was racing...
そしたらね、あの、コメント気付いてくださってね。
...and then you noticed my comment!
もう、とっても嬉しかったです！こよりもですし、見てた助手くんたちもものすごく…
I was so incredibly happy! Not just me, but all the Joshu-kuns watching too...
もう、嬉しくて、やっぱり、あの、見ていただけるっていうのが、スアラさんとか、あの、アクアプラスさんもそうですし、
We were so thrilled. Having you, Suara-san, and Aquaplus watch us...
その、公式の皆さんに、ご覧いただけるって本当に嬉しく恐縮なことなので…
...having the official staff watch us is truly an honor and a privilege...
もう、幸せでございました！ありがとうございました！
I was so happy! Thank you so much!
もうすごい楽しくて、見入っちゃいました、本当に。
It was so much fun, I was completely glued to the screen.
すごい長時間、配信されてるのがすごいなと思って本当に。
I was really amazed that you streamed for such a long time.
はい、もうそのね、その日の夜も歌枠も聞かせていただいたりとか。
Yes, and I even listened to your karaoke stream that night.
もう、すごい体力だなと思いながら。
I was thinking, "What incredible stamina!"
はい、でも楽しんでる、ね。うたわれるものが本当に素晴らしい作品だったから、
But it's because "Utawarerumono" is such a truly wonderful series.
ですね！ですので、そのうたわれるものとずっと付き合っていらっしゃる、スアラさんですけども、
Yes! And you have been involved with "Utawarerumono" for a long time, Suara-san,
推しキャラとかっていらっしゃるんですか？
do you have a favorite character?
推しキャラですか？推しキャラはやっぱりちょっと…エルルゥってことに…
A favorite character? I suppose my favorite would have to be... Eruruu...
エルルゥ！ってことに？
Eruruu! "Have to be"?
っておかないとね、ちょっとフォークで刺されるかもしれない…
I have to say that, or else I might get stabbed with a fork...
あははは！あれ？でも、もしかして、あの、仲が良い…そう、
Ahahaha! Oh, but perhaps is it because you are close friends with...
そう、中のね、中の人…柚木涼香さんとね、とっても仲良くさせていただいてて、
Yes, I am very close friends with her voice actress, Ryoka Yuzuki-san.
本当にあの、アニメのあの、放送のときからですね、
Really, ever since the anime broadcast back then,
あの、2006年からずっと仲良くさせていただいてる… / おおー！20年！
we've been close friends since 2006. / Oh, 20 years!
そうですね、20年！ / すごいー！
Yes, 20 years! / Amazing!
はい。それはエルルゥ推し、 / ですね！
Yes. So of course I'm an Eruruu fan,
ですね、ということもあって、エルルゥ推しということで、お願いします。
...so let's go with Eruruu as my favorite, please!
こよりはもう、アルルゥが大好きなので、エルルゥ、アルルゥで！
Koyori absolutely loves Aruruu, so we have Eruruu and Aruruu!
姉妹で！ / 姉妹で！嬉しいです！
The sisters! / The sisters! I'm so happy!
はい、ということで、もっともっとお話ししたいんですけども、お時間が来てしまいまして。
Yes, and though I'd love to talk much more, our time is up.
もう、本当に今日は一緒に歌っていただき、ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for singing with me today!
ありがとうございました。こよりさんの本当に柔らかい、優しい、ね、温かい、
Thank you. Being wrapped in Koyori-san's truly soft, gentle, and warm...
声にこう包まれながら、私も一緒に歌えて、本当に幸せでした。
...voice while singing together made me truly happy.
恐縮でございます！
I'm so honored!
またぜひ、色々とご一緒させていただける機会があれば、嬉しいです。 / ぜひぜひ、よろしくお願いします！
I'd love to have more opportunities to work together again. / Yes, please, absolutely!
ありがとうございました！ということで、スアラさんでしたー！ありがとうございました！
Thank you! And that was Suara-san! Thank you so much!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
こよりのリズムラボ
[Koyori's Rhythm Lab]
9th リミックス
[9th Remix]
やがて女はきれいになるだろう
Eventually, girls will become beautiful, right?
おっけー とまー！ / おっけー とまー！
Ok, stop! / Ok, stop!
だいスキ！ / だい、だい、だいスキ！
I love you! / I really, really love you!
みっつん！
Three!
おっかなびっくりでの 人生 / やった！
A timid life... / Yeah!
本当の自分に出会えない / やった！
...I can't meet my true self. / Yeah!
あのダンスがセクシー 憧れのオンナノコ
That sexy dance, my dream girl...
ドキドキしちゃう 誰かを愛すって素敵ね
My heart races. Loving someone is so wonderful.
輝きたい 愛されたい
I want to shine, I want to be loved.
歴史が放っておかない / やった！
History won't just leave us be... / Yeah!
華やかな人生 生きたい
...I want to live a glamorous life.
あぁ 悲しい歌 流れる
Ah, a sad song is playing...
街の中 歩く
...as I walk through the town.
涙が流れちゃうの
Tears start to flow...
どうしてなのだろう / ワン、ツー、スリー、フォー！
...I wonder why. / One, two, three, four!
ワン、ツー、スリー、フォー！
One, two, three, four!
誰を信じればいいのだろう
Who should I believe in?
泣きたいだけ泣けばいい / みっつん！
You should cry as much as you want. / Three!
ワン、ツー、スリー、フォー！ / ワン、ツー、スリー、フォー！
One, two, three, four! / One, two, three, four!
だからちょっと恋をして
So, fall in love a little...
お気に入り口ずさんで
...humming your favorite tune.
周りが見えなくなってもいい
It's okay even if you lose sight of everything else.
だいスキ！ / だい、だい、だいスキ！
I love you! / I really, really love you!
こっち見て！ / やった！
Look over here! / Yeah!
マジだいスキ！ / だい、だい、だいスキ！
I seriously love you! / I really, really love you!
だいスキ！ / だい、だい、だいスキ！
I love you! / I really, really love you!
みっつん！
Three!
愛♡スクリーム!
Love Scream!
アイスクリーム... クリーム...
Ice cream... cream...
教えて もっと あなたのこと
Tell me more about yourself
Tell me も・も・も Tell me も・も・も
Tell me more, more, more! Tell me more, more, more!
聞かせて もっと あなたの声
Let me hear more of your voice
Let me hear も・も・も Let me hear も・も・も
Let me hear more, more, more! Let me hear more, more, more!
こんなに ドキドキ もう 責任とれない
My heart is pounding so much, you've got to take responsibility!
Oh, I need you! Oh, Oh, I need you!
友達は卒業 運命の私
No longer just friends, I am your destiny
見つけてほしいの
I want you to find me
One! 勇気を出して
One! Gather up your courage!
Two! 見つめる作戦
Two! The staring strategy!
Three! 目と目が合えば
Three! Once our eyes meet...
Four! 止められない
Four! I won't be able to stop!
Yeah Yeah Yeah! この恋 この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah! With this love, with this romance,
Melt Melty とけちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm going to melt away!
ねえ ねえ ねえ 気づいて my darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling!
届け 大好き
Sending you all my love!
愛・スクリーム 愛・スクリーム 叫びましょう
Ai Scream, Ai Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream! Ice cream!
愛・スクリーム 愛・スクリーム 叫びましょう
Ai Scream, Ai Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream! Ice cream!
こよりちゃん！
Koyori-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
マヨネーズ！
Mayonnaise!
よりも、あなた！
More than that... you!
あずきちゃん！
AZKi-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
こしあん、つぶあん...
Smooth red bean paste, chunky red bean paste...
よりも、あなた！
More than those... you!
らみちゃん！
Lamy-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
お酒よりも...
More than alcohol...
あなた！
You!
みんな！
Everyone!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き...
Of course we love...
こ・よ・り！
Ko-yo-ri!
止められない
Can't be stopped!
Yeah Yeah Yeah! この恋 この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah! With this love, with this romance,
Melt Melty とけちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm going to melt away!
ねえ ねえ ねえ 気づいて my darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling!
届け 大好き
Sending you all my love!
愛・スクリーム 愛・スクリーム 叫びましょう
Ai Scream, Ai Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream! Ice cream!
愛・スクリーム 愛・スクリーム 叫びましょう
Ai Scream, Ai Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream! Ice cream!
お願い 見つけて my darling
Please find me, my darling!
my darling my darling
お願い 気づいて my darling
Please notice me, my darling!
my darling my darling
One! 勇気を出して
One! Gather up your courage!
Two! 近づく作戦
Two! The approaching strategy!
Three! 手と手が触れて
Three! If our hands touch...
Four! 止められない
Four! I won't be able to stop!
Yeah Yeah Yeah! この恋 この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah! With this love, with this romance,
Melt Melty とけちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm going to melt away!
ねえ ねえ ねえ 気づいて my darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling!
それは あなた！
And that's you!
愛・スクリーム 愛・スクリーム 叫びましょう
Ai Scream, Ai Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream! Ice cream!
愛・スクリーム 愛・スクリーム 叫びましょう
Ai Scream, Ai Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream! Ice cream!
愛・スクリーム 愛・スクリーム 叫びましょう
Ai Scream, Ai Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream! Ice cream!
愛・スクリーム 愛・スクリーム 叫びましょう
Ai Scream, Ai Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream! Ice cream!
La-la-la-la-la-la-la...
La la la la la la la...
もう何十回も何百回も 進む空見上げて
Dozens of times, hundreds of times, looking up at the sky...
たどり着いた場所が 夢のダイヤモンド
...the place we finally reached is the diamond of our dreams.
何千回も何万回も 涙流した君へ
To you, who has shed tears thousands, tens of thousands of times,
ねえ 諦められたことはあったかい？
tell me, was there ever a time you could just give up?
憧れは限界突破 もういらないよ弱気
My aspiration breaks through limits, I have no more use for cowardice.
そこに立ち止まるなんて もったいないでしょ
Standing still in a place like that is such a waste, isn't it?
それぞれの物語 交差する瞬間を
The moments where our respective stories intersect...
見つめる日々は
...are what we spend our days gazing at.
放て 夢だけ 大きな声 抱いて
Unleash only your dreams, holding onto a loud voice,
弾けそうな きらめきを
with a sparkle that seems ready to burst.
消えることなく どこまででも
Without ever fading, no matter how far,
世界の向こうに 届けてよ
deliver it to the other side of the world.
終わることのない この胸の衝動は
This endless impulse in my chest...
どうしたってどうしたって 僕らを呼んでいたから
...no matter what, because it has been calling out to us.
その先へと 走り続ける
Toward what lies ahead, I will keep running,
次へ、次へ
to the next, to the next!
妄想だった 中途半端な不安抱えて
It was a delusion, harboring half-hearted anxiety,
立ち尽くしていた独り 雨はプレリュード
standing still all alone, the rain is a prelude.
何千回も 何万回も 挑み続けた君へ
To you, who has kept on challenging thousands, tens of thousands of times,
ねえ 聞かせてよ 夢は叶うんだって
hey, let me hear you say that dreams do come true.
諦めが簡単ならば 絶対にないよ涙
If giving up were easy, there'd surely be no tears.
誰に邪魔させようと ためらわないで
No matter who tries to get in the way, do not hesitate.
託された情熱を 落とさずに繋いでいく
I will pass on the passion entrusted to me without letting it fall,
最終回まで
all the way to the final inning.
グラウンドに近い 星の下 煌めいて
Shining under the stars close to the ground,
鳴り止まない ファンファーレ いつも心に 流れていた
the fanfare that never stops ringing was always flowing in my heart.
遠い未来へ 祈るよ
I pray toward the distant future.
忘れられない あの日々の後悔も
Even the regrets of those unforgettable days...
追いかけて 追いかけて 滑り込んだ この想い
Chasing after, chasing after, this feeling that slid in,
青い空に 歌溢れてた 遠く遠く
singing overflowed into the blue sky, far, far away.
目覚めては繰り返す 眠い朝は
Waking up to a repeating sleepy morning,
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tightly fasten the tie around my collar.
教室のドアくぐるとほんの少し
When I pass through the classroom door,
胸を張って歩き出せる
I can puff out my chest and walk with a bit more pride.
手を振った
I waved my hand,
よかったね、と
saying, "Good for you"
廊下の隅見下ろす 掃除の途中
I look down at the corner of the hallway in the middle of cleaning
おかしなものだと思う
I think it is really a very strange thing
あたしの中の時は止まってるのに
Even though the time inside of me has already suspended
違う日々を生きてるように
As if living through different days
埃は雪のように降り積む
The dust is falling and rolling like white snow
待ってる気がした
I realized you're waiting
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I realized you keep on calling me
震えだす 今この時が
Now in this time that started to tremble
見つけた気がした
I realized I have found it
失われた記憶が 呼び覚ました
My long lost memories are already recalled
物語
That was my story
永遠の
Of eternity,
その終わり
It's almost ending
いつの間にか
Before I knew it,
駆け出してた
I started to run again
あなたに手を引かれてた
You pulled my hand and kept on running
昨日とは遠く 明日はすぐ
Yesterday far away, tomorrow right ahead
そんな当たり前に 心が踊った
That natural fact made my heart keep on dancing
聞こえた気がした
I realized that I heard it
感じた気がしたんだ
I realized I felt it already
震えだす 今この胸で
Now in my chest that starts to tremble again
もう来る気がした
I realized it was coming
幾千の朝を越え 新しい陽が
A new sun overcame a thousand of mornings
待ってる気がした
I realized you are waiting
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I realized you keep on calling me
震えてるこの魂が
However, my soul will not ever stop trembling
見つけた気がした
I realized I have found it
幾億の夢のように 消え去る日を
I saw off the day that is able to disappear like millions of dreams
見送った
I saw it off,
手を振った
I waved my hands,
ありがとう、と
saying, "Thank you" to you
ぽつり 灯り 管制塔 砂嵐の向こうへ
A faintly lit control tower toward the other side of the sandstorm
祈るように 綴った これからのこと
Things to come written down like a prayer
ラジオネーム 匿名希望 お便り届いてますか
Radio name anonymous requested, has my message reached you?
この世界がいつからか まるで他人事のように
Since when did this world feel like someone else's business?
やけに静かなので 不安になったのです
Because it is so terribly quiet, I became anxious
思い出したのです
And I remembered
人知れず口を噤んだまま
While keeping my mouth shut without anyone knowing
終われないのです それは嫌なのです
I cannot let it end, I hate that
夢ってもっと わがままだったでしょう
Dreams were supposed to be more selfish, weren't they?
応えてよ、笑ってよ、気付いてよ
Answer me, laugh at me, notice me
此処に居るのにな、意地悪だな
Even though I am right here, you are being mean
誰にも届かない光を
What should I do with this light that reaches no one?
どうしたら、伝えられるのでしょう
How can I convey it?
どうしても、伝えたいよ
No matter what, I want to tell you
ラジオネーム 匿名希望
Radio name: Anonymous
意気地なしなのでしょうか
Am I just a coward?
それともこの世界には
Or is it that in this world...
僕は お邪魔でしょうか
...I am in the way?
だとしても綴るよ
Even if that's the case, I'll still write.
みっともなく縋るよ
I'll cling on, even if it looks pathetic.
振られたって好きだよ
Even if I'm rejected, I still love you.
いいでしょ
That's okay, right?
楽しかったよね
It was fun, wasn't it?
悔しかったよね
It was frustrating, wasn't it?
もう独り言は 嫌だ
I don't want to talk to myself anymore.
「待たせちゃったかな」
"Did I keep you waiting?"
「別に待ってないよ」
"I wasn't really waiting."
夢と呼んだそれも僕らだっただけ
Even what we called a dream was just us.
もういいかい
Are you ready?
応えてよ、笑ってよ、気付いてよ
Answer me, laugh with me, notice me.
此処に居るのになあ
Even though I'm right here...
意地悪だなあ
...you're so mean.
誰にも届かない光を
A light that reaches no one...
僕だけは光と呼び続ける
...only I will continue to call it light.
真夜中 管制塔から
From the control tower at midnight...
あなたを明かしてやる
...I'll reveal you to the world.
【特報】
[Special Bulletin]
歌：博衣こより
Vocal: Hakui Koyori
作詞・作曲：堀江晶太
Lyrics & Composition: Horie Shota
新アニメーションMV
New Animation MV
応えてよ、笑ってよ、気付いてよ
Answer me, laugh with me, notice me.
此処に居るのになあ 意地悪だなあ
Even though I'm right here, you're so mean.
誰にも届かない光を
A light that reaches no one...
どうして耐えられるのでしょう
How can I bear this?
どうしても伝えたいよ
I really want to convey it to you.
管制塔より
From the Control Tower
ライブ終了直後 プレミア公開
Premiering right after the live stream!
ということで！
And with that!
新曲のお披露目、フルアニメーションMV公開の告知、新3Dのお披露目！
The reveal of my new song, the announcement of the full MV, and my new 3D showcase!
3個、ドドンとまとめてやらせていただきましたー！
I got to present all three of these in one big package!
イェーイ！
Yay!
情報量多かったけど、追いついてるかな？
It was a lot of information, but are you guys keeping up?
はい、ちょっとね、新3Dが可愛すぎて気になっちゃうと思うんですけど、
I know you might be distracted because the new 3D is just too cute, but...
まずはオリ曲の話からさせてください！
...first, please let me talk about my original song!
お披露目させていただいたのは、
The one I just performed was...
新曲「管制塔より」！
...my new song, "Kanseitou yori"!
はい！ついに、あの堀江晶太さんに書き下ろしていただきました！
Yes! I finally got the one and only Horie Shota-san to write it for me!
みんな、どうだったー？
How was it, everyone?
エモい？よかった！
Emotional? I'm so glad!
はい、そしてですね、今ちょうど映像も流して「すごい！」って言ってくれてて、めっちゃ嬉しいんですけど、
Yes, and seeing everyone watch the video and say "Amazing!" makes me so happy!
このライブ終了直後にフルアニメーションMVがプレミア公開されます！
Directly after this live stream ends, the full animation MV will premiere!
多分もう、あのマネちゃんがポチってしてくれてると思います！
I'm sure my manager has already clicked the button for it!
世界観がめちゃくちゃこだわられている映像作品になっているので、
The video has an incredibly detailed world-building, so...
何回も見たり聴いたり、そしてちょっと世界観の考察とかしてみてくださーい！
...please watch and listen to it many times and try theorizing about its world!
そして！お待たせしました！
And now! Thank you for waiting!
あ、ちょっと待って！一個言い忘れました！
Oh, wait a second! I forgot to say one thing!
さっきの曲「管制塔より」、24時にリリースもあります！よろしくお願いします！
The song "Kanseitou yori" will also be released digitally at midnight! Please look forward to it!
そしてですね、お待たせしました！新3Dー！
And now, sorry to keep you waiting! The new 3D!
どう？可愛い？可愛い？可愛いー？
What do you think? Is it cute? Cute? Cute?!
はい！もっとね、余すことなく見せたいんだけど、
Yes! I want to show you every single detail, but...
ももこママのあの、いつものにすごいくつ、近くなったんじゃないかなーと思います！
...I think it got much closer to Momoko-mama's art style!
この後のメン限ライブでね、撮影会もしまして、さらに細かく見せちゃうので、
I'll be doing a photo session during the member stream to show it in even more detail...
ぜひメン限ライブも来てください！
...so please make sure to join the members-only stream!
メン限ライブでは、本編で歌えなかったあのゲームの、みんなが大好きな曲、
In the members-only stream, I'll sing a song from that game that everyone loves...
「きん・きん・きん・きん」も歌うよ！お楽しみに！
...I'll be singing "Kin Kin Kin Kin" too! Look forward to it!
じゃあ、１つだけ新3Dのめちゃくちゃ変わったポイントを教えちゃうと...
Well then, let me share just one incredibly special feature of this new 3D...
ケモ耳が揺れます！
My animal ears move!
うおー！
Whoa!
可愛いーー！
So cute!!!
ということでね、
So with that said...
あ、あとトレンド1位本当にありがとうございます！
Oh, and thank you so much for getting me to #1 on trending!
今日無理かなって思ってたんでめちゃめちゃ嬉しかったし、
I thought it might be impossible today, so I'm incredibly happy,
トレンド爆散、なんかすっごいいっぱい入ってたみたいで
and trending exploded, with so many terms getting on there!
本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much!
それでは！もう1つ、大事な、お知らせです！ドン！
Now then! I have one more important announcement! Boom!
博衣こより誕生日記念グッズ2026が発売されます！イェーイ！
Hakui Koyori's Birthday Celebration Goods 2026 are now on sale! Yay!
早速、詳細を見ていきましょう！まず1つ目はこちら！
Let's take a look at the details right away! First up is this!
もふこよにもなる！2Wayブランケット！
The 'Turns into Mofukoyo! 2-Way Blanket'!
お部屋でゲームを楽しんでいるこよりの描き下ろしイラストです！
It features a newly-drawn illustration of Koyori enjoying games in her room!
イラストはもちろん、ももこママ！
The illustration is, of course, by Momoko-mama!
これ、丸めるともふこよに早変わりして、
If you roll this up, it quickly turns into Mofukoyo,
持ち運びも楽ちんだし、そのまま飾っても可愛いですね！
making it easy to carry around, and it's super cute to display too!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ボイスキーホルダー 〜ゲーム実況編〜！
The 'Voice Keychain: Game Let's Play Edition'!
待望のボイスキーホルダーが出ました！
The long-awaited voice keychain is finally here!
こよりの録り下ろしボイスが入っているもので、
It features newly recorded voices of Koyori,
今回はライブに合わせて、ゲーム実況中っぽいセリフ、
and this time, to match the live stream, it has lines that sound like a game Let's Play,
絶叫、が6種類入っております！
screams and all, with 6 different types included!
セリフはこよが考えました！
Koyo came up with all the lines!
イラストはなもり先生です！
The illustration is by Namori-sensei!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
こより監督ぬいぐるみスマホスタンド！
The 'Director Koyori Plushie Smartphone Stand'!
あのこより監督がついにぬいぐるみになったよ！可愛い！
That Director Koyori is finally a plushie! So cute!
そのまま飾るもよし、スマホスタンドにもなるので超便利です！
You can display it as is, or use it as a smartphone stand, which is super convenient!
絶対にゲットしてね！
Make sure to grab one!
最後はこちら！
Last but not least, this!
ゲーム機風カードホルダー！
The 'Console-style Card Holder'!
特典のチェキ風ブロマイドとか、
You can fit the bonus instax-style bromides,
ホロカも入れられて持ち運べちゃうカードホルダーです！
or Holocards in it, making it a great card holder to carry around!
中に入っている台紙のイラストは、こよちゃんが書き下ろしました！
The illustration on the backing card inside was drawn by Koyo-chan!
ゲーム機風のデザインもレトロゲームっぽくて可愛くない？
Isn't the console-style design cute and retro-game-like?
はい！そしてフルセット特典はこちらです！
Yes! And here are the Full Set Purchase Bonuses!
ももこママ描き下ろしのチェキ風ブロマイドが付きます！
It comes with an instax-style bromide newly drawn by Momoko-mama!
数量限定版は直筆サインと箔押し、箔押し複製メッセージ入り、
The Limited Quantity Edition has a handwritten signature and a foil-stamped duplicated message,
通常版は箔押しなしの複製サインとメッセージ入りになってます！
while the Standard Edition features a duplicated signature and message without foil stamping!
販売開始がこのあと21時10分に
Sales will begin shortly after this,
してあるので、皆さんあの慌てないで大丈夫です！
at 21:10, so please don't panic, it's alright!
10分からなので！
It starts at 21:10!
はい、あの、見てっててください。よろしくお願いします！
Yes, please go check it out. Thank you!
さらに、特典ASMRボイスも付きます！
Furthermore, a bonus ASMR voice is also included!
毎年恒例の、君の誕生日を逆に祝っちゃうASMRボイス2026版！
It's our annual tradition: the ASMR Voice 2026 Edition where I celebrate YOUR birthday instead!
こちらですね、毎年みんな誕生日まで我慢して聴いて、
Everyone waits patiently for their birthday to listen to this,
「わーい！」ってなってくれているの、すごく嬉しく思ってます！
and seeing you all go 'Yay!' makes me so happy!
ぜひゲットしてください！
Please be sure to get it!
はい、ということで、
Alright, so...
怒涛のお知らせでしたが、
that was a flood of announcements, but...
可愛いでしょ？みんなが可愛いって言ってくれてて、
Cute, right? Hearing everyone call them cute...
こよ嬉しいよ！
...makes Koyo so happy!
表情とかもちょっと変わったんですよ！
Also, my facial expressions have updated a bit!
にゃっ！
Nyah!
あ、これができる様になりました！
Ah, I can do this now!
あとは、キッ
Also, a...
キリッ、いぇーい！こんな表情もできるようになりました！
...determined face! Yay! I can make this expression now too!
メンゲンお楽しみに！
Look forward to the member-only streams!
ということで今日は博衣こより生誕ライブ2026、ゲームソングライブに見に来てくれて
So, thank you so much for coming to watch Hakui Koyori's Birthday Live 2026, the Game Song Live today!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
このあとはですね、新曲のアニメMV公開とメンゲンライブ、
After this, we have the premiere of the new anime MV and the member-only stream.
アニメMV公開見て、
So watch the anime MV premiere,
で、10分からグッズ買って、
then buy the goods starting from 21:10,
15分からメンゲンライブって感じで、
and then the member-only stream starts at 21:15,
ゆっくり順番に行けるようになっているので、
so it's scheduled so you can take your time going through them step-by-step.
慌てず、駆けず、
Please don't rush, don't run,
なんだ、押さず、でよろしくお願いします！
and don't push! Thank you!
ということで今日は、ちょっと遅れちゃったんだけど、
So today, even though we started a bit late,
あの、3Dお披露目して、生誕ライブもできて、
we had the 3D reveal, did the Birthday Live,
大好きなゲームソングいっぱいお披露目できて、嬉しかったよ！
and I was so happy to show off so many of my favorite game songs!
みんな本当に見に来てくれて、ありがとう！
Thank you so much to everyone for coming to watch!
また会おうね！
Let's meet again!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
MV見てね〜！
Be sure to watch the MV!
生誕 Live 2026 / 今年も応援＆お祝いありがとう
[Ending Card: Birthday Live 2026 / Thank you for supporting and celebrating this year too!]
念願のゲームソングライブ！楽しんでもらえたらいいなぁ / みんなの笑顔が見たいからいろんなコトを乗りこえて頑張るよ！好きでいてくれてありがとう
[Ending Card: The game song live of my dreams! I hope you enjoyed it. / I'll work hard to overcome anything to see your smiles! Thanks for loving me!]
絶対絶対あきらめない！！の心で一緒に歩もうね！！ / 大好ちだよ
[Ending Card: Let's walk together with the spirit of 'Never, ever giving up!!' / I love you so much!]